Guide to the Papers of Harrison Salisbury,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III: Box Listing (unsorted)
  - Ted Solotaroff (Harper & Row), 1980 (Box 96)
  - Vladimir Solovyov and Elena Klepikova, 1980-2, 87 (Box 96, 100, 104, 119)
  - Martin Sommers (Saturday Evening Post), 1960, 62 (Box 18, 23)
  - Susan Sontag (copy), 1988 (Box 121)
  - Soong Ching Ling, 1993 (Box 136)
  - Soong Ching Ling Fondation, 1993, 93* (Box 136, 139)
  - Soros Foundation, 1989, 92 (Box 124, 132)
  - Gene Sosin (Radio Liberty), 1962, 64, 69-71, 73, 76-7, 87, 90, 93* (Box 23, 28, 47, 52, 57, 69, 83, 87, 119, 126, 139)
  - Lauren K. Soth, 1965, 67, 70, 81 (Box 31, 38, 52, 100)
  - Southern Illinois University Press, 1980 (Box 96)
  - Michael Sovern, 1984 (Box 112)
  - Ann Sperber, 1986 (Box 117)
  - Frieda J. Spiller (Curtis Brown), 1968-9 (Box 43, 47)
  - Gary Spokes (SANE), 1962 (Box 23)
  - Leroy Stahl, 1974 (Box 74)
  - Stallin (HBO special), 1992 (Box 132)
  - Boris M. Stanfield, 1959-61, 63-6, 69, 78-9 (Box 16, 18, 23, 28, 31, 34, 47, 92)
  - Margaret Stanley, 1982, 89-90, 92 (Box 104, 124, 126, 132)
  - Stanley Foundation, 1993 (Box 136)
  - Frank Stanton (US Advisory Committee on Information), 1968 (Box 43)
  - Eugene S. Staples (Ford Foundation), 1971 (Box 57)
  - Winnie Stark, 1977 (Box 87)
  - John Starr (McGraw-Hill), 1958 (Box 15)
  - S. Frederick Starr, 1978-80, 83-4, 89 (Box 92, 96, 108, 112, 124)
  - Harold Stassen (subject), 1978-9 (Box 92)
  - State Historical Societ of WI, 1987 (Box 119)
  - Jean Stein, 1987, 93* (Box 119, 139)
  - Dieter Steiner (Stern), 1973 (Box 69)
  - Stan Steiner, 1983-4 (Box 108, 112)
  - Sterling Publishing, 1993 (Box 136)
  - Betsy Sternberg, 1976 (Box 83)
  - Adlai Stevenson Papers, 1973 (Box 69)
  - James Stewart-Gordon (Readers Digest), 1964, 68, 71 (Box 28, 43, 57)
  - Walter J. Stoessel, Jr. (Dep. Sec. of State), 1982 (Box 104)
  - John Stoessinger (UN), 1969-70 (Box 47, 52)
  - Muriel Stokes, 1986 (Box 117)
  - Jeremy Stone, 1970, 72-3, 78-9 (Box 52, 62, 69, 92)
  - Shepard Stone (Ford Foundation), 1965 (Box 31)
  - James J. Storrow, Jr. (The Nation), 1967 (Box 38)
  - Rex Stout, 1993 (Box 136)
  - Gladys Guggenheim Straus (Mrs. Roger), 1972 (Box 62)
  - Donald B. Straus (re Council on Foreign Relations), 1988 (Box 121)
  - Roger W. Straus, 1969-72, 82 (Box 47, 52, 57, 62, 104)
  - Harold Strauss (Knopf), 1966, 68 (Box 34, 43)
  - Stravon Publishers, 1965-6 (Box 31, 34)
  - Anna Louise Strong (subject), 1970 (Box 52)
  - John Strong and Robbin Strong (re Anna Louise), 1970 (Box 52)
  - Tracy B. Strong (re Anna Louise), 1980 (Box 96)
  - Rose Styron (Mrs. William), 1972, 74, 90 (Box 62, 74, 126)
  - Su Sun (re Soong Ching Ling), 1972 (Box 62)
  - J.-C. Suares, 1976, 78-9, 81, 83, 88-90 (Box 83, 92, 100, 108, 121, 124, 126)
  - Success (magazine), 1985 (Box 115)
  - Walter Sullivan, 1988-9 (Box 121, 124)
  - Arthur Ochs Sulzberger (xerox memo), 1971, 73 (Box 57, 69)
  - Arthur Ochs Sulzberger, Jr. (Mr. and Mrs.), 1981, 1993* (Box 100, 139)
  - Carol Sulzberger (Mrs. Arthur O.), 1974 (Box 74)
  - C. L. Sulzberger (letter to), 1969 (Box 47)
  - David Sulzberger, 1992 (Box 132)
  - Iphigene Ochs Sulzberger (Mrs. Arthur H.) (letter to-- photocopy), 1969, 75 (Box 47, 79)
  - Anthony Summers (BBC), 1971, 74, 76 (Box 57, 74, 83)
  - Sun, Soong Ching Ling (Mme. Sun Yat-sen) (letter to), 1978-9 (Box 92)
  - David Susskind, 1963-4 (Box 23, 28)
  - Elizabeth Sutherland (Simon and Schuster), 1962-4, 68 (Box 23, 28, 43)
  - Han Suyin, 1992 (Box 132)
  - Howard Swearer (Harvard Visiting Comm.), 1974, 76, 80, 86 (Box 74, 83, 96, 117)
  - Sweden, 1974 (Box 74)
  - Swedish Academy, 1992 (Box 132)
  - Swedish Embassy, 1973 (Box 69)
  - Eric P. Swenson, 1964, 67-8 (Box 28, 38, 43)
  - George Swiers (Vietnam Veterans of America), 1984 (Box 112)
  - John Temple Swing, 1966, 93* (Box 34, 139)
  - Stanley M. Swinton, 1960, 64, 67-8, 70 (Box 18, 28, 38, 43, 52)
  - Herbert Bayard Swope (family of), 1958 (Box 15)
  - Thomas Synnott, 1980 (Box 96)
  - Raymond Szabo (C&O RR), 1969 (Box 47)
  - Jim and Chris Szili, 1978-81, 83, 88, 93 (Box 92, 96, 100, 108, 121, 136)
  - Strobe Talbott, 1988 (Box 121)
  - Gay Talese, 1966, 69, 80-1, 91-2, 93* (Box 34, 48, 96, 101, 129, 132, 140)
  - Nan Talese, 1992 (Box 132)
  - Truman M. Talley (Weybright and Talley), 1969 (Box 48)
  - Henry Tanner, 1964-9 (Box 28, 31, 34, 39, 43, 48)
  - Pat Tapp, 1977-80, 82 (Box 88, 92, 96, 105)
  - Alexandre Tarsaidze, 1958, 64-5, 67, 69-70, 72-3, 75-7 (Box 15, 28, 31, 39, 48, 53, 63, 69, 79, 83, 88)
  - TASS, 1965 (Box 31)
  - Roger Tatarian (UPI), 1964-5, 68, 72, 81 (Box 28, 31, 43, 63, 101)
  - Michel Tatu, 1983 (Box 109)
  - William Taubman, 1981 (Box 101)
  - Frank E. Taylor (McGraw-Hill), 1966 (Box 34)
  - Sally Taylor, 1980, 89, 91 (Box 96, 124, 129)
  - Telford Taylor, 1978-9 (Box 92)
  - Judd L. Teller, 1964, 67, 70-1 (Box 28, 39, 53, 58)
  - Victor Temkin (Bantam), 1971 (Box 58)
  - Frances Tenenbaum (Houghton Mifflin), 1989 (Box 124)
  - Leonard Tennyson (The European Community), 1968 (Box 43)
  - Studs Terkel, 1969, 90, 93* (Box 48, 126, 140)
  - Ross Terrill, 1980, 92, 93* (Box 96, 132, 140)
  - Thailand, Royal Thai Embassy, 1993 (Box 136)
  - Thames TV, 1990 (Box 126)
  - Harry E. T. Thayer (State Dept., Asian Communist Affairs), 1969 (Box 48)
  - Theatre for Ideas, 1972-3 (Box 63, 69)
  - Athan Theoharis, 1987, 91 (Box 119, 129)
  - Louisa Theron (Council on Foreign Relations), 1989 (Box 124)
  - Werner Thiers (Mazomanie [WI] Historical Society), 1975, 77-80, 84 (Box 79, 88, 92, 96, 112)
  - This Month, 1962-3 (Box 24)
  - Cecil Thomas (National Committee on US-China Relations), 1968 (Box 43)
  - Evan Thomas, 1955, 59-72, 74, 76-9, 82, 85-6, 90, 93* (Box 14, 16, 18, 24, 28, 31, 34, 39, 43, 48, 53, 58, 63, 75, 83, 88, 92, 105, 115, 117, 126, 140)
  - Evan W. Thomas, 1976 (Box 83)
  - Lowell Thomas: Copy, 1993 (Box 136)
  - Norman Thomas, 1960 (Box 18)
  - Mims Thomason (Pres, UPI), 1964 (Box 28)
  - Edward W. Thompson, 1982-3 (Box 105, 109)
  - Hunter S. Thompson, 1978-9 (Box 92)
  - Kenneth W. Thompson, 1978-80, 83, 86 (Box 92, 96, 109, 117)
  - Ralph Thompson, 1960, 68-9 (Box 18, 43, 48)
  - James C. Thomson (Nieman Foundation), 1975 (Box 79)
  - Phintso Thonden (Office of Tibet), 1966 (Box 34)
  - Ludmilla Thorne, 1972, 76, 78-9 (Box 63, 83, 92)
  - Thunder's Mouth Press (assorted materials), 1990 (Box 126)
  - Times Literary Supplement (letters to), 1969, 71-2, 75, 77, 83 (Box 48, 58, 63, 79, 88, 109)
  - Richard L. Tobin (Saturday Review ), 1967 (Box 39)
  - Albert Todd (re Yevtushenko), 1970 (Box 53)
  - Regina Todd, 1970-1, 73-9 (Box 53, 58, 69, 75, 79, 83, 88, 92)
  - Helen Toigo, 1978-9 (Box 92)
  - John Toigo, 1971-5 (Box 58, 63, 69, 75, 79)
  - Rudolf Tokes, 1974 (Box 75)
  - Tolstoy Foundation, 1974, 85, 92 (Box 75, 115, 132)
  - Seymour Topping, 1964-6, 71-2, 76, 92, 93* (Box 28, 31, 34, 58, 63, 83, 132, 140)
  - Judge Edwin Torres, 1983 (Box 109)
  - Hiram Torres, 1987 (Box 119)
  - James V. Toscano, 1965-7, 69-71 (Box 31, 34, 39, 48, 53, 58)
  - Samuel A. Tower, 1962-3 (Box 24)
  - Amor Towles, 1972, 77-81, 83 (Box 63, 88, 92, 96, 101, 109)
  - Tran Tuong Nhu, 1980 (Box 96)
  - Tran Van Dinh, 1993 (Box 136)
  - Transaction, Inc. 1975-6 (Box 79, 83)
  - John C. Traphagen, 1964, 69-70 (Box 28, 48, 53)
  - Donald W. Treadgold, 1980 (Box 96)
  - Trilateral Commission, 1974 (Box 75)
  - Garry Trudeau and Jane Pauley, 1981-2, 93* (Box 101, 105, 140)
  - Harry S Truman (family of), 1972-3 (Box 63, 69)
  - Barbara Tuchman (eulogy), 1991 (Box 129)
  - Robert C. Tucker, 1965,67-9, 82 (Box 31, 39, 43, 48, 105)
  - Ruth Turkow-Kaminska, 1981 (Box 101)
  - Gordon Turner, 1974 (Box 75)
  - Sandra Turner (Esquire), 1967 (Box 39)
  - Stansfield Turner, 1993 (Box 136)
  - Wallace Turner, 1967-9, 88-9, 91, 93, 93* (Box 39, 43, 48, 121, 124, 129, 136, 140)
  - TV Guide, 1974, 82, 86-7, 92 (Box 75, 105, 117, 119, 132)
  - Twentieth-Century Fund, 1977 (Box 88)
  - United Nations (open letters to), 1992 (Box 132)
  - UNESCO, 1982 (Box 105)
  - UN We Believe, 1961, 73 (Box 18, 69)
  - USA Today, 1989 (Box 124)
  - Alan Ullman (Book-of-the-Month Club), 1967 (Box 39)
  - Universe Publishers (re Elizabeth Pond), 1981 (Box 101)
  - University of Chicago Press, 1975, 78-9, 91 (Box 79, 92, 129)
  - University of Connecticut, 1975 (Box 79)
  - University of Illinois, 1977 (Box 88)
  - University of Miami, 1976 (Box 83)
  - University of Minnesota, 1978-9, 92 (Box 92, 132)
  - University of Virginia Student Legal Forum, 1976 (Box 83)
  - University of Washington, 1993 (Box 136)
  - Marion Urry, 1960 (Box 18)
  - US Advisory Committee on Information, 1993 (Box 136)
  - US Arms Control and Disarmament Agency, 1993 (Box 136)
  - US Chamber of Commerce, 1993 (Box 136)
  - US-China Peoples Friendship Assoc. 1974, 78-9 (Box 75, 92)
  - US-China Writers Conference, 1993 (Box 136)
  - USIA, 1961, 72-4, 92 (Box 18, 63, 69, 75, 132)
  - US-Russian Writers Conference, 1993 (Box 136)
  - USSR embassy, 1963 (Box 24)
  - Tokuma Utsonomiya (Japanese MP), 1969-70, 76 (Box 48, 53, 83)
  - Jack Valenti, 1971 (Box 58)
  - Elizabeth Valkenier, 1977 (Box 88)
  - Cyrus Vance (copy), 1972 (Box 63)
  - Jean Vanden Heuvel, 1970-1 (Box 53, 58)
  - Katrina vanden Heuvel, 1987 (Box 119)
  - Laurens van der Post (letter to, copies), 1971 (Box 58)
  - Vanity Fair, 1991 (Box 129)
  - Vantage Press, 1986 (Box 117)
  - Stuyvesant Van Veen (Nat'l. Inst. of Arts and Letters), 1975 (Box 79)
  - George Vassilchikov (U.N.), 1958, 77 (Box 15, 88)
  - Samuel Vaughan, 1965, 68, 71, 74-9, 81, 83, 85, 93, 93* (Box 31, 43, 58, 75, 79, 83, 88, 92, 101, 109, 115, 136, 140)
  - Roger Vaurs (French Embassy), 1966 (Box 34)
  - Ivan Veit, 1958, 1966, 71-2 (Box 15, 34, 58, 63)
  - Anatoly Verbitsky, 1977, 81, 83, 85 (Box 88, 101, 109, 115)
  - Diane Verdayne (office of Hans Heineman), 1964 (Box 28)
  - Miriam Versh, 1962-5 (Box 24, 28, 31)
  - Louise H. Vidaud, 1986-88 (Box 117, 119, 121)
  - Vietmam (subject), 1992 (Box 132)
  - Viking Press, 1984 (Box 112)
  - Village Voice, 1974-5, 78-9, 86 (Box 75, 79, 92, 117)
  - Virginia, University of, Student Legal Forum, 1972-3 (Box 63, 69)
  - Carol Vogel, 1987, 90 (Box 119, 126)
  - Ezra Vogel (et al --National Committee on US-China Relations), 1967 (Box 39)
  - Voice of America, 1983 (Box 109)
  - Solomon and Marianna Volkov, 1977-83, 85, 87-8, 90, 92-3 (Box 88, 92, 97, 101, 105, 109, 115, 119, 121, 126, 132, 136)
  - Andrei Vosnesenskii (subject), 1992 (Box 132)
  - James Voss (American Academy of Arts and Sciences), 1968 (Box 43)
  - Fred Wagner (Harper and Row), 1962-3 (Box 24)
  - Dan Wakefield, 1959, 64, 68 (Box 16, 28, 43)
  - Jean Wakeland, 1967, 71-3, 75-6, 81 (Box 39, 58, 63, 70, 79, 83, 101)
  - Adam Walinsky (office of R. F. Kennedy), 1968 (Box 43)
  - Beth Bready Walker, 1977-9, 85, 89, 93* (Box 88, 93, 115, 124, 140)
  - Ramsey Walker, 1993* (Box 140)
  - Samuel S. Walker, 1993 (Box 136)
  - Walker and Co. 1974, 87, 91-3 (Box 75, 119, 129, 132, 136)
  - DeWitt Wallace, 1965-6, 71-2 (Box 31, 34, 58, 63)
  - George Wallace (subject), 1968 (Box 43)
  - Thomas C. Wallace, 1962-4, 67, 77, 80 (Box 24, 28, 39, 88, 97)
  - Raoul Wallenberg, 1993 (Box 136)
  - Russ Waller, 1959, 67, 75, 77, 84, 86-7 (Box 16, 39, 79, 88, 112, 117, 119)
  - Theodore Waller (Grolier), 1969-71, 73-5, 77, 83 (Box 48, 53, 58, 70, 75, 79, 88, 109)
  - Frank Wallick (UAW Washington Report), 1980, 83 (Box 97, 109)
  - Maureen Walters, 1971, 74 (Box 58, 75)
  - Donald Wandrei, 1972-3 (Box 63, 70)
  - War and Peace Report, 1975 (Box 79)
  - Frederick Warburg (letters to), 1968-9, 71 (Box 43, 48, 58)
  - Martin Secker and Warburg, 1967, 70 (Box 39, 53)
  - Geoffrey C. Ward (American Heritage), 1981 (Box 101)
  - John Ware (Doubleday), 1970 (Box 53)
  - Carl Warmington, 1987-8 (Box 119, 121)
  - Grace Kennan Warnecke, 1971, 76, 88, 93* (Box 58, 83, 121, 140)
  - Ian Warner, 1992 (Box 132)
  - Silas Warner, 1992, 93* (Box 132, 140)
  - Paul Warnke, 1987, 89 (Box 119, 124)
  - Francis Warner, 1970-1 (Box 53, 58)
  - Abbot Washburn (USIA), 1955, 58-60, 62-3, 68, 88, 92 (Box 14, 15, 16, 18, 24, 43, 121, 132)
  - John Nelson Washburn, 1955, 72 (Box 14, 63)
  - A. Michael Washburn (Fund for Education in World Order), 1968 (Box 43)
  - Washburn Gallery, 1978-9 (Box 93)
  - Washington Papers, 1972 (Box 63)
  - Kira Petrovskaya Wayne, 1972, 76 (Box 63, 83)
  - Albert Weeks, 1978-9 (Box 93)
  - Fred B. Weiner, 1977-9 (Box 88, 93)
  - Harold Weisberg (re assassinations), 1966, 68 (Box 34, 43)
  - Jerome Weisner (MIT), 1969 (Box 48)
  - Dean Faulkner Wells (Yoknapatawpha Press), 1981 (Box 101)
  - Jay Wells, 1981 (Box 101)
  - Jann Wenner, 1993 (Box 136)
  - Alexander (Alec) Werth, 1962-6, 68-9 (Box 24, 28, 31, 34, 43, 48)
  - Aline Werth (Mrs. Alec), 1971, 82 (Box 58, 105)
  - Diane Wesley (Encyclopedia Britannica), 1975 (Box 79)
  - Anne Wexler (White House), 1978-9 (Box 93)
  - Victor Weybright (Weybright and Talley), 1968 (Box 43)
  - John M. Whalen, 1978-9, 81 (Box 93, 101)
  - Crawford Wheeler, 1958, 60, 62-4, 67-8, 75-9 (Box 15, 18, 24, 28, 39, 43, 79, 83, 88, 93)
  - John Wheeler, 1984 (Box 112)
  - Sir John Wheeler-Bennett, 1971, 73 (Box 58, 70)
  - Morgan Wheelock, 1974 (Box 75)
  - Joseph G. Whelan (LC), 1970, 78-9 (Box 53, 93)
  - Julia Proctor White, 1960 (Box 18)
  - Theodore H. White (copies), 1971, 74 (Box 58, 75)
  - White House, 1984 (Box 112)
  - White House Conference on Children, 1993 (Box 136)
  - Alden Whitman, 1978-9, 82-6 (Box 93, 105, 109, 112, 115, 117)
  - John Hay Whitney (re Century), 1965 (Box 31)
  - Thomas P. Whitney, 1959, 62-3, 65-8, 71-83, 91-3 (Box 16, 24, 31, 34, 39, 43, 58, 63, 73, 75, 79, 83, 88, 93, 97, 101, 105, 109, 129, 132, 136)
  - Mrs. T. P. Whitney, 1985 (Box 115)
  - Whitney Foundation, 1971-2, 74-6, 80-1, 83, 91-3 (Box 58, 63, 75, 79, 83, 97, 101, 109, 129, 132, 136)
  - Who's Who in America, 1976 (Box 83)
  - Charlews Z. Wick, 1984 (Box 112)
  - Thomas G. Wicker, 1966-7, 93* (Box 34, 39, 140)
  - Jim Wilcox (Doubleday), 1978-9 (Box 93)
  - John Noble Wilford, 1983 (Box 109)
  - Roger Wilkins (subject), 1982 (Box 105)
  - John C. Willey (William Morrow and Co.,), 1958, 67 (Box 15, 39)
  - Harold S. Williams (Institute on Man and Science), 1970 (Box 53)
  - Hugh Wilson, 1982 (Box 105)
  - Kenneth Wilson (Century ), 1987 (Box 119)
  - Norman H. Wilson, 1967, 70-3, 75-6 (Box 39, 53, 58, 63, 70, 79, 83)
  - Claire Wilson (Mrs. Norman), 1974 (Box 75)
  - Patricia Wilson, 1975 (Box 79)
  - Wiltwyck School for Boys, 1969-76 (Box 48, 53, 58, 63, 70, 75, 79, 83)
  - Bill and Betty Winchester, 1985 (Box 115)
  - Dilys Winn, 1977 (Box 88)
  - Ella Winter, 1969 (Box 48)
  - Wisconsin Historical Society, 1985, 89 (Box 115, 124)
  - Roxanne Wittke, 1980 (Box 97)
  - Charles Witzell, 1955, 58-60, 69 (Box 14, 15, 16, 18, 48)
  - Harris L. Wofford, Jr, 1960 (Box 18)
  - Thomas H. Wolf, 1960, 64, 67, 78-9, 81, 84, 86, 92, 93* (Box 18, 28, 39, 93, 101, 112, 117, 132, 140)
  - Wendy Wolf (Pantheon), 1980 (Box 97)
  - Helen Wolff (office of ), 1967 (Box 39)
  - Rep. Lester A. Wolff, 1975 (Box 79)
  - Rena Wolner (Bantam), 1971 (Box 58)
  - Arthur Wolsoncraft (Playbill ), 1959 (Box 16)
  - William A. Wood (University of Chicago Press), 1962-3 (Box 24)
  - C. Vann Woodward, 1989 (Box 124)
  - WOR (Martha Deane), 1972 (Box 63)
  - The Worker, 1993 (Box 136)
  - World Environment Report, 1977 (Box 88)
  - World Health Organization, 1993 (Box 136)
  - World Press Institute, 1968-9, 71-4, 77-81, 83-4, 86 (Box 43, 48, 58, 63, 70, 75, 88, 93, 97, 101, 109, 112, 117)
  - Al Wright (Saturday Evening Post ), 1960 (Box 18)
  - Writers Digest Books, 1982 (Box 105)
  - John Wulp (Readers Digest ), 1969 (Box 48)
  - M. S. Wyeth, Jr. 1967, 76 (Box 39, 83)
  - (New York) Yankees, 1972 (Box 63)
  - Daniel Yankelovich, Inc. 1970, 72, 76 (Box 53, 63, 83)
  - Yao Wei, 1978-80 (Box 93, 97)
  - Morton Yarmon, 1980 (Box 97)
  - Adm. H. E. Yarnell, 1955 (Box 14)
  - Addie Yates (Mrs. Sidney R.), 1976 (Box 83)
  - Daniel Yergin, 1972 (Box 63)
  - Yevgeni Yevtushenko (letter to), 1982 (Box 105)
  - Esther Yntema (Atlantic Monthly Press), 1969 (Box 48)
  - Robert H. Yoakum, 1966, 71, 76, 81-3, 86, 90, 93, 93* (Box 34, 58, 83, 101, 105, 109, 117, 126, 136, 140)
  - Yoknapatawpha Press, 1993 (Box 136)
  - Will Yolen, 1962-3 (Box 24)
  - Bruce Young (U. of Chicago Press), 1975 (Box 79)
  - Andrew Young (letter to), 1986 (Box 117)
  - Genevieve Young (Harper, Lippincott), 1960-4, 68-71, 73, 81-3, 85, 90, 92, 93* (Box 18, 24, 28, 43, 48, 53, 58, 70, 101, 105, 109, 115, 126, 132, 140)
  - B. Loring Young, 1964 (Box 28)
  - M. Norvell Young (US-Russian Writers Conference), 1992, 93* (Box 132, 140)
  - Frederick T. C. Yu, 1962-4, 70 (Box 24, 28, 53)
  - Yugoslav Information Center, 1974 (Box 75)
  - S. C. Yuter, 1970-71, 74 (Box 53, 58, 75)
  - Jerrold Zacharias (MIT, re Sakharov), 1968-9, 71, 73 (Box 43, 48, 58, 70)
  - Zahadi (Iranian Amb. to US), 1978-9 (Box 93)
  - Darryl Zanuck, 1993 (Box 136)
  - Edmund Zawacki, 1958, 60, 64, 67, 73, 78-9 (Box 15, 18, 28, 39, 70, 93)
  - Tom Zetterstrom, 1981-2, 93* (Box 101, 105, 140)
  - Ata Zgoot, 1965, 87-91 (Box 31, 119, 121, 124, 126, 129)
  - Maxim Zhukov, 1991 (Box 129)
  - Yuri Zhukov (Pravda), 1975, 78-80, 82 (Box 79, 93, 97, 105)
  - Abbie Ziffren, 1974, 76 (Box 75, 83)
  - Bill Zimmerman, 1978-9 (Box 93)
  - Howard Zinn, 1963 (Box 24)
  - Arnold Zohn, 1969-70, 80 (Box 48, 53, 97)
  - Amos Zubrow (Westview Press), 1989 (Box 124)
  - Anatol Zuckerman, 1992 (Box 132)
  - Leonard Zweig, 1958-9 (Box 15, 16)
  - Helene Zwerdling (Radio Liberty), 1967 (Box 39)
  - Authors' League Authors' Guild of Symposia, 1980-1981, (Bulletins, Financial Reports, Correspondence ) (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Committee to Protect Journalists Correspondence, 1986-1993 (Box 142, Folder 9)
  - Authors' League Statements, Correspondence, etc.: Includes symposium, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Inside Story Segment on media coverage of USSR: PBS series on media -- Julia A. Whitney Fund: Festival of Russian Culture, U. of Illinois, Champaign-Urbana, Fall 1983., Jun 1982-Mar 1983, (Correspondence, Notes ) (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - Committee to Protect Journalists Correspondence, 1981-1985 (Box 143, Folder 8)
  - Authors' League Pamphlets, Correspondence, etc.: Some 'Forms' from other years, 1983 (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - Authors' League Financial Report, Correspondence, 1984 (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - Authors' League Correspondence: Includes some material on copyright idea and law, 1985 (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - Authors' League Financial Statement, Correspondence: Includes Salisbury talk on copyright, 1985-1989 (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - Khrushchev Mein Kampf, (Correspondence ) (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - China: 100 Years of Revolution, (Reviews ) (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - The Unknown War, (T.V. Show, Book, Reviews ) (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Russia: Russia in Revolution, (Correspondence, Notes, Reviews ) (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Without Fear or Favor, (Correspondence, Reviews ) (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - Without Fear or Favor: Larry King show, (Correspondence, Notes ) (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Without Fear or Favor, (Reviews ) (Box 145, Folder 7)
  - Without Fear or Favor, (Reviews ) (Box 145, Folder 8)
  - Black Night, White Snow, (Reviews ) (Box 146, Folder 9)
  - Black Night, White Snow, (Reviews ) (Box 146, Folder 10)
  - Black Night, White Snow, (Correspondence ) (Box 146, Folder 11)
  - Black Night, White Snow, (Correspondence ) (Box 146, Folder 12)
  - Concepts and research for starting morning LA and evening NYC newspapers, 1979 (Box 146, Folder 15)
  - Esquire: Travels Around America -- Controversy re corporate sponsorship of journalism a la TV, 1976 (Box 147, Folder 13)
  - The Gates of Hell: pre and post-publication, outline, some edited chapters, (Correspondence, Reviews ) (Box 147, Folder 14)
  - Publicity relating to Salisbury: Some relating to specific of Salisbury with Clark Clifford and James Reston Solo. One proof sheet includes of wife, 1980's, (Books, Photos, Proof Sheets ) (Box 148, Folder 16)
  - Whitney Foundation Financial Statement, Correspondence: Includes grants to support projects related to Russian culture, 1982-1988 (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Whitney Foundation Tax Returns, Correspondence, 1983-1990 (Box 149, Folder 5)
  - Whitney Foundation Minutes, Financial Records, Foundation Materials, 1984 (Box 149, Folder 6)
  - Whitney Foundation Tax Returns, Statement of Investments, Correspondence, 1984-1992 (Box 149, Folder 7)
  - Whitney Foundation FELS, 1977-1986, (Financial & Investment Statements, Tax Returns ) (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - Whitney Foundation Gogol Library: Relating to recipient of Whitney Foundation grant (Box 149, Folder 9)
  - Whitney Foundation Bank records (Box 149, Folder 10)
  - Curtis Brown Book, Correspondence: Regarding rights and contracts. -- Law Firm, 1986, 1987 (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Publishing Rights, 1992, (Correspondence ) (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Publishing Rights: Including copyright renewals, 1985-1992, (Correspondence ) (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - Royalties, 1990-1993 (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - Royalties, 1986-1989 (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - Without Fear or Favor, New York Times, 1969-1982, (Book, Contracts, Negotiations ) (Box 151, Folder 10)
  - Contracts, Book: Including foreign rights, 1945-1972 (Box 151, Folder 11)
  - Contracts, Book, Newspapers, 1963-1977 (Box 151, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: re lectures, 1983-1993 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Invitations, Professional Receptions, Meetings, 1992-1994 (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - Receipts, Promotion, 1992 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - Travel and Trips, 1991-1993, (Expense Receipts, Reports, Correspondence ) (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - Travel, Rome, 1990, (Expenses ) (Box 152, Folder 8)
  - China Trip, 18 Aug-6 Nov, 1987 (Box 152, Folder 9)
  - China: Black and Munro, Black Hands: Lives in the Chinese Democracy Movement, 1976-1992, (Manuscripts ) (Box 153, Folder 10)
  - China: -- Committee for National Security re Persian Gulf situation, Jan 1991 (Box 153, Folder 11)
  - China Conference: U.S.-Chinese Writers Conference: This is a biannual event, held alternately in the US and: China -- Salisbury was a participant in 1988 and 1990, Los Angeles, 1984-1990 (Box 153, Folder 13)
  - Fourth Chinese-U.S. Writers Conference, Le Shan Sichuan Province, April 1988 (Box 153, Folder 14)
  - China: -- This file includes news about Chinese dissident Fang Lizhi, photographs, an envelope for the Institute of Mechanics of the Chinese Academy of Sciences, and a Foreign Affairs article on Chinese-American relations. -- Some material is in Chinese., 1985-1993 (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Chinese (M - Q): Includes poetry, 1970-1992, (Correspondence ) (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Chinese (R - S): Includes photograph and material on Soong Ching Ling Foundation -- See also "Publicity" folder (Box 2-4, folder 16), 1985-1993, (Correspondence ) (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - Chinese (T - W): Includes photographs, 1980-1993, (Correspondence ) (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - Chinese (X - Z): Includes photographs and newspaper clippings, (Correspondence ) (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - General Chinese (A-C ), 1977-1993, (Correspondence ) (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - General Chinese (D-G) -- Includes photos of Salisbury with unidentified others, both Chinese and Western -- Planning for Chinese film documentary on "The Americans" -- Articles on 1992 US defense budget, 1981-1992 (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - Chinese (H-K): Includes book review, 1985-1992, (Correspondence ) (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - China: -- Boxer rebellion and Foundation Grigg on Sun Yat-sen -- One re Chiang Kai-Shek and new translation of Sun Tzu (Box 155, Folder 9)
  - General Chinese: Includes photograph, 1976-1993, (Correspondence ) (Box 155, Folder 12)
  - CIA Carroll, Adler, Kennedy, Vietnam, Reston, Baker, Catledge Misc. [mostly New York Times people], 1972-1979 (Box 157, Folder 3)